[{"answer": "Well, we know that there has been some -- there have been some advances made in the investigation.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 25, "question": "But what has there been today that we know for sure in terms of development?", "qSentId": 24}, {"answer": "Well, potentially it is significant.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Do we know what any of this means?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 67, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 66}, {"answer": "That's probably what you should be reading into it.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "Has there -- is there a bit of chaos behind the scenes?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "It's -- you're such a cheery individual by nature.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 128, "question": "I'm well, Piers, how are you?", "qSentId": 127}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 137, "question": "Do you know why they cancelled it?", "qSentId": 136}, {"answer": "Well, I've been briefed, and I understand some of that and other -- and other evidence that is being pursued -- you know, yesterday the FBI asked the general public to submit their own photographs and videotape.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 148, "question": "Do you know what they have seen or how clear the images are?", "qSentId": 147}, {"answer": "It's good to see you tonight, Piers.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 200, "question": "Why did you go to the marathon and how had your day been until that point?", "qSentId": 199}, {"answer": "I honestly can't tell you where I drew the power from to do that.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 212, "question": "What made you do that?", "qSentId": 211}, {"answer": "I approached an officer first and told her I had had some medical training in the past with mass casualty stuff.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "What did you see around you as you went into try and help?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "I haven't been able to make any contact with her, Piers.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 227, "question": "Have you made any contact with her?", "qSentId": 226}, {"answer": "I got her to look at me, first off.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "What is it that you were able to say to her by way of comfort in that moment of acute agony for her?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "I was actually employed by a couple oil companies working in the Gulf of Mexico on offshore drilling rigs.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "Where did you have that?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 252, "question": "Did you feel that it was usually helpful of that you had been through that?", "qSentId": 251}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 273, "question": "I believe you're currently unemployed, is that right, Tyler?", "qSentId": 272}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 280, "question": "Would you like to do that?", "qSentId": 279}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I keep on going back and forth.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 304, "question": "In terms of speculation, where is your head taking you with this investigation?", "qSentId": 303}, {"answer": "It does.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "Is it all pointing now to the hallmarks of an al Qaeda strike?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Piers, I think it's a very difficult investigation to conduct.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "What do you make of the way the FBI is conducting this so far?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I think it would depend upon how much other information they had to go along with those pictures.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "How would you be playing that if you were the FBI?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "As the -- two of the three people you spoke to just a minute ago were, it is tending toward that.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 399, "question": "Is your head moving towards al Qaeda, as many others seem to be?", "qSentId": 398}, {"answer": "Well, you defeat a network with a network.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "What do you do about that?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Not necessarily.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "Is this a failure?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "I am disgusted and so disappointed in our Senate.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "What is your reaction?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "You know, if they were to lose a loved one to a horrific tragedy like we did, they would feel the same way.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 478, "question": "If the deaths of 20 young children and your sister and five other adults at an elementary school, if that isn't enough to bring in something, what is?", "qSentId": 477}, {"answer": "I'm disgusted with it.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "Are you staggered by the reaction of fellow Americans to this?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "That they should be ashamed.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 496, "question": "What do you say to those senators that voted all this stuff down today?", "qSentId": 495}, {"answer": "Keep fighting.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 506, "question": "What do you intend to do next?", "qSentId": 505}, {"answer": "Well, you know, we got very little notice in advance.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "What was your reaction that suddenly all these people were being brought to you?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "So in what we do, we will see people with injuries like this, but what's unique about this, certainly in the civilian population, is the number of patients with such severe injuries.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 528, "question": "In terms of the severity and scale of the injuries, have you in your career ever encountered anything quite like it?", "qSentId": 527}, {"answer": "Yeah, I think this was a very unique situation.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 532, "question": "It seems extraordinary that so many were hit and yet so few, in the end, ended up losing their lives?", "qSentId": 531}, {"answer": "You know, I think it's very difficult for all of us, for all the patients.", "docId": "130417pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "How hard is it for you, as a human being, to see a five-year-old kid brought in who's been blown up by somebody, by a terrorist?", "qSentId": 549}]